seoulsemicon.com 2019-07-17

# Seoul Semiconductor | Privacy Policy

본문으로

## 

### PRIVACY POLICY

#### PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy explains how Seoul Semiconductor Co., Ltd., (“SSC”) uses and protects any information that you provide SSC when you use this website and our services. SSC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. SSC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from [09-13-2018] 

  1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
  2. USING YOUR INFORMATION
  3. SHARING YOUR INFORMATION
  4. KEEPING COLLECTED INFORMATION SECURE
  5. DATA RETENTION
  6. LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES
  7. USING COOKIES
  8. YOUR RIGHTS
  9. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF DATA

##### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect personal information about you from this website, Email or phone call

  1.     * **Request Information**
      * \- Your name, Country, Sex, Company`s name, Job title, Phone number and Email
    * **Career Information**
      * \- Your name, Phone number and other information in your job application
    * **Customer Information**
      * \- Country, Name, Company`s name, Phone number and Email
    * **Promotion Information**
      * \- Country, Name, Address, Phone number and Email
    * **Event Information(ex. Exhibition)**
      * \- Country, Name, Company’s name, Address, Fax number
    * **Servey Information**
      * \- Country, Name, Sex, Job title, Phone number and Email
  2. The categories of personal information that collected from Email or written form other than this homepage may have some differences

##### USING YOUR INFORMATION

  1. We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
  2.     * \- To provide products or services you request 
    * \- Recruitment
    * \- To contact with our customer or Sales
    * \- To provide a prize and to conduct marketing activities
    * \- To condut surveys regarding company and product brand

##### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We may share your information to SSC affiliates and carefully selected companies that provide services for or on behalf of us, such as companies that help us with system operating or development. These entities are limited by contractual provisions in their ability to use your information for purposes other than providing services for us.

We will not sell or distribute your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. When we provide your personal information to third parties with your consent beforehand, you can choose not to provide certain information. But then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.

##### KEEPING COLLECTED INFORMATION SECURE

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##### DATA RETENTION

We will not keep your personal data for longer than is necessary for the purpose it was collected or until you request us to delete. This means that data will be destroyed or erased from our systems when it is no longer required.

We may retain some of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements, to support business operations.

##### LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

##### USING COOKIES

A cookie is a small amount of data that is placed by your browser on your device. Once you agree, the data is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to visitor`s needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

##### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to request details about the information we collect about you and to request us to correct inaccuracies in that information, to object to or request the restriction of processing, to request access to, the erasure or portability of your information. Under the laws of some jurisdictions, we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.

If you request deletion of personal information, you acknowledge that you may not be able to access or use the Services and that residual personal information may continue to reside in our system records and archives for some time, in compliance with applicable law, but we will not use that information for commercial purposes.

Also you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if we do not control your personal information in accordance with our privacy policy.

##### INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF DATA

Your use of our Services will involve the transfer, storage and processing of your personal information outside of your country of residence, to Korea consistent with this policy. We will take appropriate measures, in compliance with applicable law, to ensure that your personal information remains protected. 

##### FUTHER INFORMATION

If you have any specific questions, please contact us at:

  1. \- Global : abc@seoulsemicon.com
  2. \- EU : info.europe@seoulsemicon.com
